Hello

I'm Srijana Maharjan

Female
Sydney, Australia
srizana.m@gmail.com
https://srijanamaharjan.github.io/

I started programming in high school in Q-BASIC and have done several projects in PHP, JAVA and Android. I worked at Augusta Information Solutions as PHP developer for one and a half years as junior PHP developer and at Woxweb IT Factory for 1 year and 10 months as Web developer developing WordPress plugins and customizing themes and web applications using custom PHP.

Skills

Programming Languages: JAVA, PHP

Databases: MSSQL, MySQL, Oracle

Tools: Eclipse, Netbeans, Sublime Text, GIT, SVN, Adobe Photoshop

Others: Web Development (Javascript, HTML, CSS, WordPress, LESS, jQUery, AJAX, Typescript),

AngularJS, Q-Basic.

Experience

Mar2017 - Current

The Intermedia Group - Full Stack Web Developer (Full Time)

WordPress Theme customization and error ticket handling

APR 2015 - JAN 2017

Woxweb IT Factory - Web Developer (Full Time)

WordPress Plugins Development and Theme Customization Web applications using custom PHP

Projects

A. The University of Texas Medical School at Houston

Project Description: Online distribution of website content and web-based applications for complex large departments and school, including, but not limited to creating and implementing website content and web- or computer-based systems.

Responsibilities: Develop the website with the use of WordPress Custom post Types to create menu.

Used: PHP, WordPress , SublimeText , LESS, GIT, CPT

B. Lalitpur District Court

Project Description: A website for the district court of lalitpur for lawyers to share, communicate and collaborate information.

Responsibilities: Develop the website, support and training to users.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

C. Wisefemales

Project Description: An online magazine with online store and discussion forums.

Responsibilities: Develop the website using WordPress and build custom plugins.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

D. This world music

Project Description: A site for promotion of African traditional music with music mixers and online store

Responsibilities: Develop the website in WordPress and the music mixers using HTML5

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText, HTML5

E. Setxmarketing

Project Description: A website for liquor promotion business with representative portal.

Responsibilities: Develop the website in WordPress and custom tools for exporting tasting reports.

Used: PHP, WordPress, SublimeText

SEP 2013- MAR 2015

Augusta Information Solutions- PHP Developer (Full time)

Worked as junior PHP developer with involvement on big projects such as Online Examination System

Projects

A. Online Examination System

Project Description: An Online Examination System for Lucky Education Center that helps conduct academic examinations.

Responsibilities: Develop models and views for different user roles and user management module.

Used: PHP, Eclipse, SVN, MySQL

B. NamasteService

Project Description: Online shopping store with integrated payment gateways

Responsibilities: Develop the front-end and modules for integration of facebook, mailchimp widgets.

Used: PHP, jQuery, Eclipse, SVN, MySQL

Education

SEP 2013 - JAN 2017

University of Central Lancashire - BSc (Hons) Business Computing and Information System

2010 - 2013

Golden Gate Higher Sec School- High School